Crone, Michelle; Papers apap101
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Subject Files, 1927-1998, Undated; 5; 12.3 cubic ft.
  - Testimony Presented to the Governor's Task Force on Lesbian and Gay Issues, joyce Hunter, 1985 (Box 22 (5-Subject Files), Folder 57)
  - Three hula hoops decorated and tied together with yarn, rope and fabric, Undated (Box 35 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Through the Looking Glass: a gynergenetic experience, Boston April 23, 24, 25 (22in by 28in), 1976 (Flat-file 4, Folder 1)
  - T.W.E.E.D New Works Festival, Program, 1994 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 58)
  - Unidentified Photographs, slides, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 59)
  - "Violet painting," on back: drawing, "Witches of the Nite Burnin" (13in by 20in), ca. 1984 (Oversized 6, Folder 1)
  - Virgin Islands Mental Health Reports, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 60)
  - Virgin Islands, Photographs, Undated (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 61)
  - Virgin Islands "Project Introspection: Legends and Myths", books, 1969 (Box 14 (5-Subject Files), Folder 62)
  - Virgin Islands, Saint Thomas, Undated (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 1)
  - Wallflower Order Dance Collective poster, Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 5)
  - Washington Park Conservancy, Undated (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 2)
  - Ways in Being Gay Film Festival, 1990 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 3)
  - Wimmin Fest, program, 1990 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 4)
  - White cotton gloves, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - "WNYC Celebrates Gay and Lesbian Pride Month", 1991 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 5)
  - Women Against Racism (WAR), fliers, notes, 1982; Undated (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 6)
  - Women Alive, Networking Festival, 1990 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - The Women's Building, 1986-1988 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 8)
  - Women's Fun Festival, flier, 1990 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 9)
  - Women's Motorcycle Festival, leaflet, 1985 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 10)
  - Women's Pentagon Action, Undated (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 11)
  - Women's Pentagon Action Poster, Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 3)
  - Womenworks Conference on Women in the Arts, program, 1979 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 12)
  - Womongathering Festival, 1989 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 13)
  - Womonwrites, 1986-1989 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 14)
  - Workshops, leaflets, programs, 1985-1985; Undated (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 15)
  - Writings, 1980; 1985-1984 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 16)
  - Yellow plastic beads, Undated (Box 31 (5-Subject Files), Folder 7)
  - "You Are Not Alone" poster - written: "To Michelle and Susan, Love, Thank you for all your work, Love Judy and Harriet[?], Undated (Oversized 3, Folder 2)
  - Young and Teen Peacemakers, 1988 (Box 15 (5-Subject Files), Folder 17)
- Periodicals, 1972-1998, Undated; 6; 4.2 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by publication title
  The Periodicals series consists of newspapers, magazines, newsletters, and other regular publications from all over the United States and some foreign countries concerning the lesbian and gay community and activism events. This material seems to have been collected by Michelle Crone during her career and travels.
  - 10 Percent, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - All About Austin, 1990 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - Almanac for Social Justice, Albany, 1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Amazon Times, Owings Mills, Maryland, 1991-1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Amazonas, 1981 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Among Friends Newsletter, Dallas, 1988 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - Apex, Albany, 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - ASTRAEA Bulletin, 1991 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - B&G: A Different Point of View, 1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - Bay Area Reporter, San Francisco, 1987 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Bay Area Women's News, Oakland, 1987 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Bay Windows, Boston, 1986 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Berkshire Women's News, Pittsfield, Massachusetts, 1986-1987 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - Between the Lines, Detroit, 1995 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - BLK, 1989; 1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - Boston Women's Fund, 1986 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - Capitol Newsletter, Washington, D.C., 1982 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - Catskill Mountain Womyn's World Drum & Percussion Happen'n, 1988 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - The Center Fold, Orlando, 1991 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - Chicago Outlines, 1988 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - Chorus Lines, New York, 1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - Clarion, Tucson, Arizona, 1984 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - Coming Up!, San Francisco, 1986-1989 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - CommUnity, Albany, 1972; 1987-1990; 1992-1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 14)
  - CommUnity, Albany, 1994-1996; 1998 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 15)
  - Community Connections, Asheville, North Carolina, 1994 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - Community Voice, West Palm Beach, Florida, 1995 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 16)
  - Connection, Southern Connecticut State, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 17)
  - Connexus, West Hollywood, 1989-1990 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 18)
  - CORE, Long Beach, California, 1990; 1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 19)
  - Crisis, Baltimore, 1995-1996 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 20)
  - The Daily Women, Albany, 1977 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - Dallas Voice, 1994 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - Dare. Nashville, 1988 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 14)
  - Deneuve, San Francisco, 1991; 1993-1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 21)
  - Diversity with a Difference, Los Angeles, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 22)
  - Dykes, Disability & Stuff, Boston, Undated (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 23)
  - Dykespeak, San Francisco, 1993; 1995 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 15)
  - Equal Times, Babylon, New York, 1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 24)
  - Etcetera, Atlanta, 1989; 1991 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 25)
  - Fellowship, Newburgh, New York, 1978 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 26)
  - Feminist Lesbian Social Group News, Sunnyvale, California, 1986 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 16)
  - Feminist Voices, Madison, Wisconsin, 1990 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 17)
  - The Fine Line, Syracuse, New York, 1988 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 27)
  - First Link, Seattle, 1991 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 28)
  - Fleming, Tamulevich & Associates Winter Newsletter, Ann Arbor, 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 29)
  - Fountain, Miami, 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 30)
  - The Front Page, Raleigh, 1992 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 18)
  - The Gay Community News, Honolulu, 1980-1984; 1987 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 31)
  - The Gay Community News, Honolulu, 1988 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 31)
  - Gay & Lesbian Times, San Diego, 1994 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 19)
  - Gayzette, Utica, New York, 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 32)
  - The Gazette, Florida, 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 33)
  - Girljock, San Francisco, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 34)
  - The GLAAD Bulletin, New York, 1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 35)
  - GLPCI Network, Washington, D.C., 1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 36)
  - GLRVC In The Light, Camarillo, California, 1990 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 37)
  - Hag Rag, Wisconsin, 1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 38)
  - Hagborn, Albany, 1980-1981 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 20)
  - Harrisburg Area Women's News, 1984 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 39)
  - Hera, Binghamton, New York, 1992 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 21)
  - The Herland Voice, Oklahoma City, 1990 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 40)
  - Hot Wire, Chicago, 1991-1993; 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 41)
  - IGLA Bulletin, Hollywood, California, 1991; 1995; 1997 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 42)
  - ILIS Bulletin, Amsterdam, 1986-1988 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 43)
  - In The Life, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 44)
  - In The Life, Wappingers Falls, New York, 1994 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 22)
  - Info News, Syracuse, 1985 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 45)
  - Jane Doe, Binghamton, New York, 1985 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 46)
  - Just Out, Portland, Oregon, 1989 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 23)
  - Lambela Rising News, Washington, D.C., 1991; 1994 (Box 18 (6-Periodicals), Folder 24)
  - The Lambda Strategy, Undated (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 47)
  - Lap Notes, New York, 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 48)
  - The Lavender Calendar, Olympia, Washington, 1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 49)
  - Lavender Web, Asheville, North Carolina, 1991-1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 50)
  - Lesbian Community Network, Orlando, 1988-1990; 1992-1993; 1995-1996 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 51)
  - Lesbian Connection, East Lansing, Michigan, 1980-1982; 1984 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 52)
  - Lesbian Connection, East Lansing, Michigan, 1986-1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 53)
  - Lesbian Connection, East Lansing, Michigan, 1990-1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 54)
  - Lesbian Connection, East Lansing, Michigan, 1994-1998 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 55)
  - Lesbian Contradiction, Minneapolis, 1988 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - Lesbian and Gay Historical Society of San Diego Newsletter, 1995 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 56)
  - Lesbian Network, Rozelle, Australia, 1986-1987 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 57)
  - The Lesbian News, Los Angeles, 1994 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Lesbian Resource Center, Seattle, 1989 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 58)
  - Lesbian Tide, Los Angeles, 1978; 1980 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 59)
  - Lesbian World, Euclid, Ohio, 1992 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Lesbians in Colorado, Denver, 1992 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Mama Bear's News & Notes, Oakland, 1987-1989 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - Matrix, Santa Cruz, California, 1990 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - Metroline, Hartford, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 60)
  - Mountain Laurel, Berkeley Springs, West Virginia, 1989-1991 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 61)
  - Nashville Scene, 1990 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - The National Alliance, New York, 1987 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - National Women's Studies Association 17th Annual Conference Bulletin, 1996 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 62)
  - The New Censorship, Denver, 1993 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 63)
  - New City: The Magazine for a Drug Free Los Angeles, 1996 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 64)
  - New Directions for Women, Englewood, New Jersey, 1988-1989; 1991 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - New Women's Times, Rochester, 1980 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - The News, Atlanta, 1987 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - The News, Atlanta, 1991 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 65)
  - NLFO News, Los Angeles, 1979 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 66)
  - Of a Like Mind, Madison, Wisconsin, 1984-1985 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - Off Our Backs, Washington, D.C., 1985-1987; 1989 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - On Our Backs, San Francisco, 1991; 1994 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 67)
  - On the Scene, San Diego, 1987 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 14)
  - The Other Voice, SUNY Binghamton, 1986 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 15)
  - Out Magazine, New Mexico, 1990 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 68)
  - Outlines, Chicago, 1991 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 16)
  - Outlook, San Francisco, 1990; 1992 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 69)
  - Outweek, New York, 1990-1991 (Box 16 (6-Periodicals), Folder 70)
  - Outwrite, London, 1984; 1986 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 17)
  - Philadelphia Gay News, 1988; 1995 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 18)
  - Plexus, Oakland, 1985 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 19)
  - Pride Path, Buffalo, New York, 1994 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - Query, Tennessee, 1995 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 20)
  - Quest, Denver, 1992 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 21)
  - Re-Evaluation Sisters, Seattle, 1978 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Relax, Folks! Dream!, Liberty, Tennessee, 1993 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Resist, Boston, 1989 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Revolutionary & Radical Feminist Newsletter, Leeds, UK, 1986 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - San Francisco Bay Times, 1991 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 22)
  - San Francisco Sentinel, 1988 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 23)
  - Sappho's Isle, New York, 1989-1990 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 24)
  - SCWU, West Hollywood, California, 1985 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - Seps, Greensboro, Vermont, 1990 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - Sistership, Crow's Nest, Australia, 1988 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - Sojourner, Jamaica, 1980; 1991; 1995 (Box 19 (6-Periodicals), Folder 25)
  - Southern Feminist, Athens, Georgia, 1985 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 1)
  - Southern Voice, Atlanta, 1988-1989 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 2)
  - Southern Voice, Atlanta, 1990-1993 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 3)
  - Stonewall Union Reports, Columbus, Ohio, 1989; 1990 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 4)
  - Tales From the Closet, Comic Books, 1987 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - Themis, Los Angeles, 1980 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - THRF News, Austin, Texas, 1991 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - Tribe, Toronto, 1995 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 5)
  - Turn Out, 1992 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - Two Eagles, Minneapolis, 1990 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - Valley Women's Voice, Amherst, Massachusetts, 1985; 1988 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 6)
  - Voice, Albany, NY, 1985 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 14)
  - Washington Blade, 1987; 1993 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 7)
  - Wavelength, Seattle, 1986; 1988 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 15)
  - What She Wants, Cleveland, 1988 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 16)
  - What She Wants, Cleveland, 1993 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 8)
  - Wire's New Collection, New York, 1989 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 17)
  - The Women's Alternative Times, Austin, Texas, Undated (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 18)
  - Women's Building News, Albany, 1988; 1991-1993 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 19)
  - Women's Cancer Resource Center News, Berkeley, California, 1993 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 20)
  - Women-Centered News, Albany, 1980; 1986 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 9)
  - Women-Centered News, Albany, 1988-1990 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 21)
  - Women's History Network News, Santa Rosa, California, 1987 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 22)
  - Women and Networking, Trenton, 1987 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 23)
  - Women Strike for Peace, Washington, D.C., 1995 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 10)
  - WomaNews, New York, 1981; 1985; 1987 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 11)
  - Women of Power, Boston, 1984; 1987-1988 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 24)
  - Womenspirit, Wolf Creek, Oregon, 1975; 1978; 1981 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 25)
  - Wommin Together, North Carolina, 1984 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 26)
  - Xenogeny, Nashville, 1995 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 12)
  - Xtra!, Toronto, 1995 (Box 20 (6-Periodicals), Folder 13)
  - Zenger's, San Diego, 1995 (Box 17 (6-Periodicals), Folder 27)
- Audio, 1979-1995, Undated; 7; 1.25 cubic ft.
  Alphabetical by perfumer
  This series includes unassociated audio, including cassette tapes, CDs, and a 7 inch phonographic record. Many of these items are demos used by Michelle Crone to select performers for the various festivals and events she organized.
  - ADA - Opportunity Knocks More Than Once, 1989 (Cassette 4)
  - Addie - The Joke's On Me, Somethin' New, Undated (Phonograph-record 1)
  - Beth Adams - Olivia, Undated (Cassette 5)
  - Altazor, 1989 (Cassette 6)
  - Felicity Artemis Flowers and Ruth Barrett - Invocation to Free Women, 1987 (Cassette 7)
  - Burning Blue Soul - Soul Mining, Undated (Cassette 8)
  - Lorraine Bates - A Texas Gal, Undated (Cassette 9)
  - Melody Beattie - Beyond Codependency, Undated (Cassette 10)
  - Begonia, 1993 (Cassette 11)
  - Begonia - Like It Is, 1990 (Cassette 12)
  - Laura Berkson, 1989 (Cassette 13)
  - Karen Beth - To Each One of Us, 1989 (Cassette 14)
  - Karen Bilik, 1994 (Cassette 15)
  - Billy Tipton Memorial Saxophone Quartet - Saxhouse, 1993 (Cd 1)
  - Wendy Binkowitz - The Best We Have, 1993 (Cassette 16)
  - Suhir Blackeagle - The Healing, 1993 (Cassette 17)
  - Bongwater - The Power of Pussy, 1990 (Cassette 18)
  - J. Breat and Samis Rose - Take Two, 1987 (Cassette 19)
  - Bright Morning Star - Sweet and Sour, 1988 (Cassette 20)
  - John Bucchino - Solitude Lessons, 1990 (Cassette 21)
  - Burning Times - Rumors of the Big Wave, 1992 (Cassette 22)
  - Michael Callen - Living in Wartime, 1988 (Cassette 23)
  - Carole and Bren - Thirteen Ships, Undated (Cassette 24)
  - Betty Carter - Now It's My Turn, 1988 (Cassette 25)
  - Laura Catullo - Coyote Oldman, 1991 (Cassette 26)
  - Teresa Chandler - Druthers, 1990 (Cassette 27)
  - Teresa Chandler and Karen Ripley - I Survived a Femme!, 1993 (Cassette 28)
  - Zenobia Conkerite, 1994 (Cassette 29)
  - Zenobia Conkerite, 1994 (Cassette 30)
  - Anne Coombs, 1979 (Cassette 31)
  - Catie Curtis - From Years to Hours, 1991 (Cassette 32)
  - Cross Current - Not Goin' Back, 1992 (Cassette 33)
  - Cross Current, 1990 (Cassette 34)
  - The Deadly Nightmares, Undated (Cassette 35)
  - Deb Criss - Heartbeat, 1990 (Cd 2)
  - Del Rey - Live!, 1991 (Cassette 36)
  - Sandy DeLegal - We Are Women, 1990 (Cassette 37)
  - Melanie DeMore - Come Follow Me, 1986 (Cassette 38)
  - Lisa Dempsey, Undated (Cassette 39)
  - Destiny - Destiny, 1990 (Cassette 40)
  - Melinda DeMaio - Dyke Dramas, 1994 (Cassette 41)
  - Die Schrollmanner - Pacific Tour, 1993 (Cd 3)
  - Disappear Fear: Live at the Bottom Line, 1992 (Cd 4)
  - Pansy Division - Undressed, 1991 (Cassette 42)
  - Larry Dvoskin - Songs, Undated (Cassette 43)
  - Ellen James Society, 1992 (Cassette 44)
  - Maria Esposito, 1994 (Cassette 45)
  - Melissa Etheridge - Labels PSA, 1995 (Cassette 46)
  - Melissa Etheridge - Yes I am, 1993 (Cassette 47)
  - Exit 154 - Demo, 1991 (Cassette 48)
  - Dos Fallopia - My Breasts Are Out Of Control, 1992 (Cassette 49)
  - A Family of Friends - Women's Music Sampler, 1993 (Cassette 50)
  - Robin Ferguson, 1994 (Cassette 51)
  - Festival Tape 2 Spring 86', 1986 (Cassette 52)
  - Debbie Fier - In Your Hands, Undated (Cassette 53)
  - Sue Finx - True Life Adventures, 1989 (Cassette 54)
  - Marianne Flemming, 1990 (Cassette 55)
  - Marianne Flemming - III Chords and a Bridge, 1994 (Cd 5)
  - Flirtations Live - Out On The Road, 1992 (Cassette 56)
  - Rebecca Coupe Franks - All of a Sudden, 1992 (Cassette 57)
  - Freyda and the Atta Boys, Undated (Cassette 58)
  - Judi Friedman - Arc of Diamonds, 1986 (Cassette 59)
  - Karen Friedman - Silicone Rap, 1992 (Cassette 60)
  - Mary Gemini - Crazy…For You, 1990 (Cassette 61)
  - Mary Gemini, 1982 (Cassette 62)
  - Mary Gemini - For Interpreter, Undated (Cassette 63)
  - Susanne Gerull - Beware of the Cat!, Undated (Cassette 64)
  - Ronnie Gilbert - The Spirit is Free, Undated (Cassette 65)
  - Girls in the Nose, 1990 (Cassette 66)
  - Girls in the Nose - Origin of the World, 1992 (Cassette 67)
  - Marga Gomez, 1989 (Cassette 68)
  - Monica Grant - The Heart of It, 1991 (Cassette 69)
  - Monica Grant - Harbor Girl, 1989 (Cassette 70)
  - Lisa A. Gray, Undated (Cassette 71)
  - Connie Grauer - Short Stories, Undated (Cd 6)
  - Halcyon - Before and After, 1992 (Cassette 72)
  - Halcyon, 1990 (Cassette 73)
  - Pam Hall Demo, Undated (Cassette 74)
  - Paul Hallesy, Undated (Cassette 75)
  - HARP, Undated (Cassette 76)
  - Susan Herrick - Truth and the Lie, 1991 (Cassette 77)
  - Here's Iris…Dust Mopping The Corners of Consciousness, 1987 (Cassette 78)
  - Helen Hooke - Verse-ability, 1988 (Cd 7)
  - Catherine Hughes - Blowing Up a Storm For Lesbian Liberation, 1993 (Cassette 79)
  - I was born this way, Undated (Cassette 80)
  - Iabis Traditional Brasilian Band, Undated (Cassette 81)
  - The It Twins, 1993 (Cassette 82)
  - Cheryl Jacobs, 1992 (Cassette 83)
  - Jelsa, 1989 (Cassette 84)
  - Nedra Johnson, 1991 (Cassette 85)
  - Julie, Undated (Cassette 86)
  - Andrea Katz, 1993 (Cassette 87)
  - Andrea Katz - Painted Dreams, 1993 (Cassette 88)
  - Andrea Katz - Why, 1993 (Cassette 89)
  - Mary Kelley, 1988 (Cassette 90)
  - Knock Out, 1993 (Cd 8)
  - Lisa Koch - Colorblind Blues, 1991 (Cassette 91)
  - Sally Landers and the Flirtations, 1991 (Cassette 92)
  - Zoe Lewis - Tired...but Inspired, 1988 (Cassette 93)
  - Lijada Sisters, Undated (Cassette 94)
  - Laura Love, 1991 (Cassette 95)
  - Mare, Undated (Cassette 96)
  - Mare, Undated (Cassette 97)
  - Marla BB - Blues, 1991 (Cassette 98)
  - Marla BB and Band - Live, in concert!, 1988 (Cassette 99)
  - Marla BB - Sassy Mama Blues, 1993 (Cassette 100)
  - Me, Her, and Her, Undated (Cassette 101)
  - Milestones, Undated (Cassette 102)
  - Suse Millimon - Windows and Light, 1991 (Cassette 103)
  - Melanie Morrison - The Way you Move, Undated (Cassette 104)
  - Mother's daughters - Take it to another place…, 1992 (Cassette 105)
  - Ritual Motion, Undated (Cassette 106)
  - Ritual Motion - Feel It, 1995 (Cassette 107)
  - Mrs. Fun Demo, Undated (Cassette 108)
  - New Order - Low-Life, 1985 (Cassette 109)
  - Nice - Camera Obscura, 1985 (Cassette 110)
  - Faith Nolan - Freedom to Love, 1989 (Cassette 111)
  - No Man's Land, 1993 (Cassette 112)
  - Leslie Nuchow, 1993 (Cassette 113)
  - Jess Hawn Oakenstar - Your Hear Will Show You, 1994 (Cd 9)
  - The Oh Sooo Politically Correct Players - Anita Meets the Cat On the Court, 1992 (Cassette 114)
  - The Outskirts, 1993 (Cassette 115)
  - Ruth Pelham, 1993 (Cassette 116)
  - Linee T. Perroncel, 1995 (Cassette 117)
  - Phranc - Positively Phranc, 1991 (Cassette 118)
  - Robin Plitt - Florida Daydreams, 1990 (Cassette 119)
  - Sue Popper - Indigo Line, 1993 (Cassette 120)
  - Bruce Priebe - Let Go, Undated (Cassette 121)
  - Punk Mary, Undated (Cassette 122)
  - Punk Mary - Gemini, 1982 (Cassette 123)
  - Pyramid, 1986 (Cassette 124)
  - Sandy Rapp - Where Were the Flowers, 1991 (Cassette 125)
  - Toshi Reagon - Justice, 1990 (Cassette 126)
  - Ernie Real - The Real Appeal, Undated (Cassette 127)
  - Relative Viewpoint - What will we leave the children?, 1991 (Cassette 128)
  - Reverend King, Undated (Cassette 129)
  - Happy Rhodes - equipoise, 1993 (Cassette 130)
  - RI Feminist Chorus, Undated (Cassette 131)
  - Rhythm Express, 1994 (Cassette 132)
  - Rhythm Express, Undated (Cassette 133)
  - The Rhythm Method, 1994 (Cassette 134)
  - Richie Rich, Undated (Cassette 135)
  - Terri Roben - Riverwalk and other songs, Undated (Cassette 136)
  - Andrew Roblin and the Pocono Mountain Men, Undated (Cassette 137)
  - Andrew Roblin and the Pocono Mountain Men, Undated (Cassette 138)
  - Norman Salant and Benjamin Bossi - Music from MAZES, 1989 (Cassette 139)
  - Nancy Scott Live with The Therapy Sisters, 1989 (Cassette 140)
  - Carol Seraiah, Undated (Cassette 141)
  - Anne Seale - Sex for Breakfast, 1991 (Cassette 142)
  - David Sereda - The Blue Guide, 1994 (Cd 10)
  - Sound Image - She Is!, Undated (Cassette 143)
  - Stephanie Shore - Folks on T.V., 1991 (Cassette 144)
  - Elaine Silver - Echoes of Light, 1988 (Cassette 145)
  - Elaine Silver - Wandering Woman, 1984 (Cassette 146)
  - The Slick of 76': A Musical Catastrophe - Original Cast Recording, 1986 (Cassette 147)
  - Judith Sloan, 1992 (Cassette 148)